As an only child and a geek, a late bloomer, someone who was like bullied for various reasons,
I would be bullied for all kinds of reasons. I don't like you. You talk white. I don't like you.
You light-skinned. I don't like you. You think you're smarter than everybody else. You an
encyclopedia. And I'd be like, well, I just knew the answer. So to then like grow up as an adult,
I don't even know what I'm being bullied for in this case, because they can't even get their act
together. They can't even get on the same page about like what the issue is. You know, it's just
basically like, I mean, we don't like her tone, but I just feel like what's my tone? I mean,
and there's so many people who are fine with my tone and love the tone and feel empowered by the
tone. So it's also a measure of ego when people feel like, well, my version of this is the version
that matters. But I will say as that person who has always kind of been in the space of having a
target, it's like a really big deal to feel supported in this way. I've never been supported
in this way in my life. And it's not a small thing.